{
    "collection": "kata-basic",
    "name": "Katakana",
    "subtitle": "カタカナ",
    "items": [
        {
            "id": "kata-a",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ア",
            "back": "a"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-i",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "イ",
            "back": "i"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-u",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ウ",
            "back": "u"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-e",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "エ",
            "back": "e"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-o",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "オ",
            "back": "o"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ka",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "カ",
            "back": "ka"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ki",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "キ",
            "back": "ki"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ku",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ク",
            "back": "ku"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ke",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ケ",
            "back": "ke"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ko",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "コ",
            "back": "ko"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-sa",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "サ",
            "back": "sa"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-shi",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "シ",
            "back": "shi"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-su",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ス",
            "back": "su"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-se",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "セ",
            "back": "se"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-so",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ソ",
            "back": "so"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ta",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "タ",
            "back": "ta"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-chi",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "チ",
            "back": "chi"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-tsu",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ツ",
            "back": "tsu"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-te",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "テ",
            "back": "te"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-to",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ト",
            "back": "to"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-na",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ナ",
            "back": "na"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ni",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ニ",
            "back": "ni"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-nu",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ヌ",
            "back": "nu"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ne",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ネ",
            "back": "ne"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-no",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ノ",
            "back": "no"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ha",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ハ",
            "back": "ha"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-hi",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ヒ",
            "back": "hi"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-hu",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "フ",
            "back": "hu"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-he",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ヘ",
            "back": "he"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ho",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ホ",
            "back": "ho"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ma",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "マ",
            "back": "ma"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-mi",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ミ",
            "back": "mi"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-mu",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ム",
            "back": "mu"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-me",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "メ",
            "back": "me"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-mo",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "モ",
            "back": "mo"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ya",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ヤ",
            "back": "ya"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-yu",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ユ",
            "back": "yu"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-yo",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ヨ",
            "back": "yo"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ra",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ラ",
            "back": "ra"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ri",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "リ",
            "back": "ri"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ru",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ル",
            "back": "ru"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-re",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "レ",
            "back": "re"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-ro",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ロ",
            "back": "ro"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-wa",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ワ",
            "back": "wa"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-wo",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ヲ",
            "back": "wo"
        },
        {
            "id": "kata-n",
            "type": "katakana",
            "front": "ン",
            "back": "n"
        }
    ]
}
